It's alive! The thing's alive!
它是活的, 这东西是活的！
(COUGHING)
He's dead!
他死了！
Keep back! It must be that smoke!
后退！肯定是这种烟雾！
(COUGHS)
Guards!
警卫！
(CHOKING COUGH)
Keep away from here!
别靠近这里！
Use the air conditioning!
打开空调！
Switch the air conditioning to expel!
将空调切到排烟模式！
(DRONING AND BUZZING)
(RASPING WHISPER) Dispose of him!
处理掉他！
- What do you mean?
- You will adjust the T-Mat controls
- 你什么意思？  - 你要调节 T-Mat 开关
and suspend him in space...
把他仍到太空中去...
..between the moon and Earth!
..在月球与地球的中央！
- Is this the right cubicle?
- It had better be!
- 就是这个格子间吗？  - 最好就是！
(FEWSHAM) Please! Please don't make me!
求你了！请别逼我！
Complete it!
快完成！
(HISSING, LABOURED BREATHING)
Oh, no!
噢, 不要！
That's the interior casing. It comes off easily.
那是内部套管, 很容易弄下来的
- Is the circuit prepared yet?
- Yes, almost.
- 线路准备好了吗？  - 是, 快了
- Almost.
- You are wasting time!
- 就快完成了  - 你在拖延时间！
- Operate!
- No!
- 操作！  - 不！
At once!
立即！
(TRILLING)
You've killed him!
你杀了他！
You've killed him! You've killed him!
你杀死了他！你杀死了他！
(HISSING, LABOURED BREATHING)
(RASPING WHISPER) Prepare to dispatch to London.
准备传送到伦敦
Do as I say!
按我说的做！
The time has come for your mission.
You understand what you must do?
是时候了, 你的人物该开始了．你明白你必须做什么吗？
I understand. (HISSES)
我明白
You must succeed at all costs.
你必须成功, 不惜一切代价
(HISSING, LABOURED BREATHING)
Transmit to London!
传送到伦敦！
I need time.
我需要时间
I must reprogramme.
需要重新编制程序
(COMPUTER) Information coming in
on appearance of vegetable blight
收到信息：出现蔬菜疫情
attacking parks and gardens
in the metropolises.
各大都市的公园和花园均有出现
(RADNOR) Guards!
警卫
(COMPUTER) ..destroying cereals.
...毁坏了谷类作物
(TRILLING BUZZ)
How much longer must I wait here?
我还得在这里等多久？
(RASPING WHISPER) Do not ask questions!
不许问问题！
I need food and rest!
我需要食物, 还有休息！
I haven't had any sleep for...
我已经很久没有睡觉了
..hours.
很多个小时
(RASPING WHISPER) What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I must fix the cubicle.
我必须先修改传送室
But you said T-Mat was functioning properly!
但你说过 T-Mat 工作很正常！
I know, but there's something I forgot.
我知道, 但有点情况我忘记了
Quick! The heating controls are over there.
快！温度调节齐就在那里
Turn the main wheel to full.
将最大那个轮子转到最大
Report to Central Control.
报告控制中心
The creature is entering the east compound area.
那个怪物已经进入了东部大院
(TRILLING BUZZ)
(RADNOR) What's happened? Report!
什么情况？赶紧报告！
Look out, Zoe!
小心, Zoe！
(TRILLING BUZZ)
(part4 ends here)